<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>塔香食譜</title>
    <link>https://blog.herearoma.com/</link>
    <description>Recent content on 塔香食譜</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <copyright>&amp;copy; 2018-2020 willliu.me &amp; herearoma</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://blog.herearoma.com/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    <item>
      <title>Post</title>
      <link>https://blog.herearoma.com/post/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 24 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.herearoma.com/post/</guid>
        <description>
        </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>關於我</title>
      <link>https://blog.herearoma.com/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Jan 2020 00:00:00 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.herearoma.com/about/</guid>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;那一天忽然出現一個想法，在這個世界，好多人都在跟人分享「怎麼做」，但卻好像很少看到背後所隱藏的邏輯跟心理、生理過程的「為什麼？」跟「怎麼辦？」剛好，我是一個習慣做簡介、還有手把手教學以及流水帳的人，分享自己的體驗，跟不同的人對話，講講底層的感覺與原因，或許更適合我。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;我是 Will，白天體驗社會，晚上思考人生，學習新的事物，練習舊的技巧，這就是我。在這裡想與你分享生命經驗，以及整合不同的工具，來幫助你規劃自己的未來，並一步步的實踐出心中藍圖。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;從來沒有自詡為靈性療癒師，但希望每個人都能療癒自己。以下轉載自巴夏所述之《成為「靈性療癒師」的關鍵點》：&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;blockquote&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Also allow yourselves to understand the following thing about healing:&lt;br&gt;
關於「療癒」，你們要明白以下幾個要點：&lt;br&gt;
Many of you are healers or have a desire to be healers of one type or another.
你們中很多人都是某種形式的療癒師，或者有意願要成為一名療癒師。&lt;br&gt;
Understand what it means to be a healer. You&#39;re not really healing anybody else directly.&lt;br&gt;
所謂療癒師，意味著：你並沒有直接療癒某個人，&lt;br&gt;
A healer creates, in whatever way they choose to, a vibrational field of energy.&lt;br&gt;
而是你以自己所選擇的方式，創造一個振動能量場。&lt;br&gt;
It does not matter what way you choose, you still create this vibrational field whether you choose to imagine it or not. It is simply the natural energy field that all of you have.&lt;br&gt;
不論你選擇什麼樣的方式，不論你​​是否運用了想像力，你時刻都在創造振動能量場，振動能量場是每個人天生所具有的。&lt;br&gt;
But it vibrates at a certain frequency that is representative of your desire and your intention to help another person.&lt;br&gt;
但你的療癒的振動能量場，它有著一定的頻率，代表著你的渴望，以及你想要幫助他人的意願。&lt;br&gt;
Therefore, it is important for the healer to be balanced as well, so the vibration of balance is in the energy field.&lt;br&gt;
所以，你的能量必須平衡，這點非常重要，只有這樣，你的能量場中才會有平衡的振動&lt;br&gt;
When you attract someone to you who wishes assistance, what you are actually doing as a healer is giving off a particular vibrational pitch for them to be immersed in.&lt;br&gt;
當你吸引某個人，前來尋求你的幫助，作為一名療癒師，你實際上做的，是將他們籠罩在你所散發出特定「振動音調」之中。
Thus, the vibrational pitch of that energy field is like an invitation to that person to match your vibration with their energy.&lt;br&gt;
你能量場中的這個「振動音調」就像一個邀請函，邀請對方將他們的能量與你的能量相匹配。&lt;br&gt;
Then, bit-by-bit, either quickly or slowly, in matching the energy of the healer, the person becomes healed by healing themselves.&lt;br&gt;
當他們選擇與你的能量相匹配，那麼他們就會一點一點地，或快或慢地，把自己療癒，恢復健康狀態。&lt;br&gt;
That is how all healing works.&lt;br&gt;
所有的療癒，都是這麼運作的！
Doesn&#39;t matter what style, doesn&#39;t matter how fast or slow the process. It&#39;s a matter of changing the vibration of the belief system of the person to be healed, so they heal themselves, with reflective assistance.&lt;br&gt;
重要的不是形式，也不是過程的快慢，重要的是你作為他們（健康的狀態的）投射，由於你的幫助，對方的信念系統改變為「自己是已經被療癒的振頻」。&lt;br&gt;
So, if you have a great desire to be a healer or to share with people, to be of service in any way, it is very important to remember that what they are mostly going to be picking up on is your vibrational pattern of balance.&lt;br&gt;
所以，如果你有強烈的願望要成為一名療癒師，或教別人如何做療癒，或為他人做任何形式的服務，那有一點非常重要，你必須記住，就是：他們從你那裡獲得的最多的是你的平衡的能量振動模式。&lt;br&gt;
Now, if you are excited about being a healer, then understand you will be able to help all those that come to you, because you have attracted them with your particular vibration.&lt;br&gt;
如果你對「成為一名療癒師」感到很興奮，那你要明白：來找你的任何人，你都能幫助他們。正是因為你的特定的振頻，你才能吸引他們前來。&lt;br&gt;
Doesn&#39;t necessarily mean that you will have the effect on them that you might expect with your mentality.&lt;br&gt;
但這並不意味著 療癒的效果一定會如你所預期的。&lt;br&gt;
But if they are attracted to you, they are attracted to you for a rea​​son and they will get something out of it.&lt;br&gt;
但如果他們受你所吸引，那肯定有某種原因，以及某種收穫，他們才會被你所吸引。&lt;br&gt;
If you are excited about being a healer but are doubtful about your ability to be of assistance to someone else, then you yourself are creating a &amp;ldquo;negative&amp;rdquo; vibration in your field.&lt;br&gt;
如果你對「成為一名療癒師」感到很興奮，但你卻懷疑自己的能力，不知道自己能否幫助對方，那你的「不相信」，就會在你的能量場創造出負面的振動。&lt;br&gt;
And of course, then you might perhaps fulfill your own prophecy and will not be able to help them.&lt;br&gt;
結果可能就是：「你實現了對自己的預言，並且沒法幫助他們。」&lt;br&gt;
But if it is truly exciting for you to be a healer in any way, then relax and trust that the vibration that you are will benefit them in some way, shape or form.&lt;br&gt;
但如果不論情形如何，你都對“成為一名療癒師”真心感到興奮，那你只需要放輕鬆，相信你的振頻會以某種方式讓對方受益。&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;/blockquote&gt;

        </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>